<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ashish Kujur: Home on Ashish Kujur</title>
    <link>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ashish Kujur: Home on Ashish Kujur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ashishkujur7.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/note/</guid>
      <description>Here are some lecture notes and assignment problems that I have written down. Admittedly, most of the them are incomplete or work in progress:
Lecture Notes in Functional Analysis Some Problems in Functional Analysis My master&amp;rsquo;s thesis on Beurling Factorisation of Hardy Spaces Some Problems in Harmonic Analysis A Review of Interpolating sequences in spaces with the complete Pick property </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashish Kujur: Contact</title>
      <link>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You may reach me via my email addresses: ashishkujur23@iisertvm.ac.in, kujur.ash@gmail.com. I try my best to reply promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashish Kujur: Interesting Links</title>
      <link>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>This is a compilation of links that I believe might be helpful to budding (function-theoretic) operator theorists:
OTTER - Operator Theory Talks for Early Researchers FOCAHA - Forum of Complex And Harmonic Analysis Complex Analysis Lab Focus Program on Analytic Function Spaces and their Applications Operator Theory Information Network Here are some lecture notes and expository articles on some topics related to Operator Theory that one may find useful:
Lecture Notes on Reproducing Kernel Hilbert Spaces by Vern Paulsen Lecture Notes on Hardy Spaces by Benjamin Eichinger Lecture Notes on Functional Analysis and Operator Theory A survey of Drury Arveson space by Michael Hartz A survey of Model Spaces by Stephan R Garcia &amp;amp; William T Ross A survey of Dirichlet Space by Nicola Arcozzi, Richard Rochberg, Eric T Sawyer, and Brett D Wick Lecture Notes on Clark Measures Pick&amp;rsquo;s Theorem-What&amp;rsquo;s the Big Deal?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashish Kujur: Publications</title>
      <link>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishkujur7.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>As of now, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing to see here. Hopefully, I will populate this empty list in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
